

# **Jacques Nalletamby**

Web Developer

**Telephone** +49 (0) 176 62233759

**Email** jacquesnalletamby@gmail.com **Address** Im Lindenhof 28, 10365 Berlin

## Profile

Frontend Web Developer driven by customer satisfaction and great frontend code.

I am a hard working individual keen to tackle user problems.

I leverage my customer service experience and frontend skills to find the right solution and make businesses successful and users happy.

# Technical Skills

HTML	••••
CSS	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Javascript	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Ruby on Rails	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Bootstrap 4	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Git Control	••••
Heroku Configuration	• • • • •

## **Experience**

Customer Service Representative January 2015 - December 2017

Chal-Tec GmbH Berlin, Germany

- Responsible for customer inquiries and complaints handling
- Answering technical queries regarding electronic products
- Handling escalated customer cases
- Logistics and returns management
- PayPal and dispute handling
- Collaboration with Business Process department for data reporting and analysis

Sound Engineer Assistant and Promoter Komedia LTD May 2013 - July 2014 Brighton, UK

- Responsible for setting up stage and room acoustics before live events
- Adjusting sound quality and volume to meet the required standard of artists
- Performing scheduled maintenance on all audio equipment
- Time management of band slots
- Promotion of events held at the venue

#### **Education**

CareerFoundry GmbH
Certificate in Web Development
July 2018 - October 2018

Berlin, Germany

- Dedicated 400+ hours to CareerFoundry's bootcamp course in Web
   Development in order to transition into careers that align with my passion for innovation and technology
- Resulted in a portfolio piece that showcases all parts of Web
   Development languages and frameworks such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript,
  jQuery, Ruby on Rails and Github

Northbrook College Worthing, UK BTEC National Diploma in Music Technology September 2010 - July 2012 Distinction (Grade 1), Distinction\* (Grade 1+)

- Dedicated 3 years learning topics such as music business management, music production and audio engineering
- Graduated in the top 3 of the class
- Proactive student of the Advanced music technology program, a music curriculum with special focus on business presentations
- Conducting technical research into music products